But, to the new financial year, as far
as the general insurance industry is
concerned, and I would particularly say
that it's been a weak start for the
listed general insurance players. That's
because, you know, the largest listed
general insurance company, ICICI Lombard
on the private side, that has
underperformed industry average growth
in the month of April by about 400 basis
points. The company has managed to grow
its premium just at about 1.7% versus
industry average of 6% growth. Another
company, New India Assurance, has grown
its premium just by 1% in the month of
April on a year-on-year basis. Industry
average, as I pointed out, is about 6%
growth. Niva Bupa, on the health
insurance side, the same story
continues. Listed players continue to
underperform. Niva Bupa growing at 35%
its health insurance premium in the
month of April. Star Health growing its
premium by 19%. Remember, on the
standalone health insurance side, the
industry average growth is about 35%.
So, two listed players there also
underperforming the industry average.
It's the unlisted large players which
have performed very strongly month of
April. So, on the general insurance
side, players like Bajaj General
Insurance, Tata AIG General Insurance,
HDFC Ergo, SBI General, IndusInd General
Insurance, all these mid-to-large
players performing ahead of the industry
average, and the listed players
underperforming.